Diane Di Prima Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
Diane Di Prima Papers.
undated, 1934-1990.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
Di Prima, Diane.
6 linear feet.
Diane Di Prima, best known for her work as a Beat poet and writer, was born 6 August 1934 in Brooklyn, New York. She attended Swarthmore College (1951-1953). Di Prima has received National Endowment for the Arts grants in 1966 for Poets Press and in 1973. She writes nonfiction, autobiographies, journals, essays, poetry and plays.
MSS19910042
Biography
Diane Di Prima is best known for her work as a Beat poet and writer, but she is also distinguished as a feminist and civil rights supporter. Born on August 6, 1934 in Brooklyn, New York, Di Prima is the only daughter and eldest child of Francis and Emma Di Prima. Di Prima's maternal grandfather, Domenico Mallozi, was an active anarchist and friend of Carlo Tresca, the famed Italian anarchist and advocate of workers rights. Mallozi's influence on his granddaughter is evident in her life and her work. In 1962, Di Prima married her first husband, writer Alan Marlowe, whom she divorced in 1969. In 1972 she married Grant Fisher whom she divorced in 1975. Di Prima is the mother of five children: Jeanne, Dominique, Alexander, Tara, and Rudra.
Because her parents were college educated, Di Prima was afforded educational opportunities that many middle-class Americans, male or female, did not during this era. It was at the prestigious Hunter College High School in New York City that she began writing. Following high school, she attended Swarthmore College for two years until 1953 when she left to immerse herself in the Bohemian lifestyle of lower Manhattan's Greenwich Village. The confluence of artistic energies in Greenwich Village provided Di Prima a setting to inspire her writing to which by now she had devoted her full attention. She is an associate of Audre Lord, Ezra Pound, Jack Kerouac, Allen Ginsburg, Lawrence Ferlinghetti, Le Roi Jones, and Timothy Leary.
Beat writers and artists, dissatisfied with the status-quo during the 1950s, distrusted authority figures and challenged cultural norms throughout their lives in an effort to promote personal freedom. The Beats experimented with new ways of thinking, medicated states, and lifestyles to enhance their understanding of the world. Di Prima by her own account experimented with drugs. She participated in former Harvard professor Timothy Leary's Millbrook, New York LSD experimentation in 1966.
Many Beat luminaries encountered difficulties with the law and the government. Diane Di Prima was no exception. She personally faced charges of obscenity on multiple occasions by the United States government concerning her work through the New York Poets Theatre and the newspaper The Floating Bear. Di Prima was initially co-editor of The Floating Bear from 1961-1963 with Le Roi Jones. From 1963-1969, she was the sole editor of the influential underground newspaper in Greenwich Village. In 1961, Di Prima was arrested by the FBI for alleged obscenity of two poems published in The Floating Bear. The case was thrown out by a grand jury. The New York Poets Theatre, an art theatre she co-founded with choreographer James Warring, operated for four seasons from 1961-1965. In 1963, The Poets Theatre was implicated in an obscenity case involving Jean Genet's movie, Chant d'Armou. She and Warring fought the government's charges. Again, Di Prima won her obscenity case against the United States. By her own accounts, she was consistently harassed by the law enforcement concerning the content of her work.
Di Prima, along with husband Alan Marlowe, founded the Poets Press in New York City (1964-1969). They designed, printed, and published books by various contemporaries. Poets Press published the first books by Audre Lord, Di Prima's high school classmate, David Henderson, Clive Matson, and Herbert Huncke. By the end of the 1960s, Di Prima moved to the west coast to continue her writing. She became involved in a commune known as the "Diggers" who provided free-food to anyone in need. She also became a follower of Zen priest Shunryu Suzuki Roshi in San Francisco. This fostered her spirituality and her studies in eastern religion.
In 1958, Di Prima published her first book of poetry, This Kind of Bird Flies Backwards. She is perhaps most well-known for her later works. Memoirs of a Beatnik, published in 1969, described her experiences as part of the Beat culture in 1950s New York. Revolutionary Letters, a series of poems in the form of letters published in 1971 concern Di Prima's thoughts on her counter-culture beliefs. Loba, published in 1973 is a mythological poem concerning a strong female protagonist with feminist, pagan, and natural world themes. This is widely considered to be her best work.
From 1971 to 1975, Di Prima traveled extensively for the Poetry-in-the-Schools program sponsored by the National Endowment on the Arts. She taught students ranging from elementary to college level. Since then, Di Prima has taught poetry primarily at the New College of California as well as the Naropa Institute for writing in Boulder, Colorado. She was one of the founders of the Jack Kerouac School of Disembodied Poetics at Naropa in 1974. In 1980, Di Prima was a co-founder and core faculty member of the Masters in Poetics Program at New College of California. Writing, as she states, is her life and she has been teaching writing techniques since the 1960s. The techniques that she teaches are similarly unique like much of her life. Di Prima encourages experimentation amongst her students in expanding their minds. This is in an effort to relate more closely to the earth, to the past, and to themselves.
Scope and Content
The collection contains primarily correspondence between Di Prima and colleagues, friends and family. Also included are journals and diaries, poetry and a manuscript of Memoirs of a Beatnik.
Arrangement
Series I: Personal and Biographical Information ( undated, 1934-1990 )
Series II: Writings ( undated, 1966-1990 )
Subseries A: Diaries ( 1966-1972 )
Subseries B: Poetry ( 1982-19900 )
Subseries C: Prose, ( 1969-1990 )
Series III: Correspondence ( undated, 1967-1990 )
Subseries A: Incoming ( undated, 1967-1990 )
Subseries B: Outgoing ( undated, 1976-1990 )
Subseries C: Other ( undated, 1985-1990 )
Series IV: Photographs and Audio Materials ( undated )
Series V: Ephemera ( undated, ca. 1980-1990 )
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of literary collections. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Separated Material
Materials separated from the collection and catalogued:
-----. No Trees. Dodd Call No.
-----. The Psychology of Rubber. London: Natural Rubber Company, 1964. From Peter Hartman's library. Dodd Call No.
----. Üvöltés. Vallomások A Beat-Nemzedékröl. Dodd Call No.
A.I.H.A. Newsletter. October 1989.
American Book review. v. II, #4, May-June 1980; v. 12, #3, July-August 1990.
Before Columbus Review. A Quarterly Review of Multicultural Literature. V. 1, #2/3, Fall/Winter 1989.
Il Caffè. October 1981.
City Arts Monthly. July 1980. 2 copies.
City Miner. V. 4, #2, 1979.
Colorado State Review. New Series v. V, #1, Spring 1977.
Community Writers' Project, Inc. v. 1, #2, Spring 1988.
CWG Newsletter. 1990
Dahl, David. Panic Hour. Santa Barbara, CA: Tsunami Press, 1984. Inscirbed to Di Prima by author. Dodd Call No.
Directory of American Poets. 1975 Edition. Directory of American Fiction Writers. 1976 Edition.
Folio. March 1988, April 1990.
Forum.. September/October 1988.
Fra Noi. V. XXVI, March 1987.
Grazide, Richard Somebody Get Us a Ladder Up Here. 1988 Dodd Call No.
Jarnot, Lisa. The Fall of Orpheus. A Special copy for Diane di Prima. Number 11 of a limited edition. Buffalo, NY:Lisa Jarnot, 1989. Dodd Call No.
Naropa Institue Update. Summer 1989.
Naropa Weekly. Issues 1, September 1989.
PEN Oaskland Newsletter. October 1989, March 1990.
Poet News. October 1988, June 1989, February-November 1990.
Poetry Flash. #153, December 1985; #177, December 1987.
Poetry Project. #133, 137 1989-1990.
Poetry USA. V. 4, #16, Fall 1989. 2 copies.
Poets & Writers, Inc. 1977 Supplement.
Reporter. State University of New York at Buffalo. V. 19, #22, 24 March 1988.
Scoop, The Press Club of San Francisco. V. 39, # 16, 4 September 1989.
Stone Drum. V. 1, #4, Spring 1986. Laid in note from editor.
Word Out! V. 3, #2, Winter 1990; v. 4, #1, Fall 1990.
Bibliography
About the Author:
Books (Selected)
This Kind of Bird Flies Backward. New York: Totem Press, 1958.
Dinners and Nightmares. New York: Corinth Books, 1961.
The New Handbook of Heaven. San Francisco: Auerhahn Press, 1963.
Poets Vaudeville. New York: Feed Folly Press, 1964.
Hotel Albert: Poems. New York: Poets Press, 1968.
Alan S. Marlowe. Earthsong: Poems 1957-1959, New York: Poets Press, 1968.
L.A. Odyssey. San Francisco: Poets Press, 1969.
Memoirs of a Beatnik. New York: Olympia Press, 1969.
Revolutionary Letters. San Francisco: City Lights Books, 1971.
Kerhonkson Journal, 1966. Berkeley: Oyez, 1971.
The Calculus of Variation. San Francisco: Privately printed, 1972.
Loba, Part I. Santa Barbara: Capra Press, 1974.
Freddie Poems. Point Reyes, CA: Eidolon Editions, 1974.
Selected Poems 1956-1975.,; enlarged as Selected Poems: 1956-1976. Plainfield, VT: North Atlantic Books, 1977.
Loba Part II. Point Reyes, CA & Kathmandu, Nepal: Eidolon Editions, 1976.
Loba: Parts I-VIII. Berkeley: Wingbow Press, 1978.
Plays
“Murder Cake”, New York, Living Theatre, 1960.
“Paideuma”, New York, Living Theatre, 1960.
“The Discontentment of the Russian Prince”, New York, New York Poets Theater, 1961.
“Like”, American Theatre for Poets, 1964.
“Monuments”, New York, Cafe Cino, 1968.
“Discovery of America”, New York, Theater for the New City, 1972.
“Whale Honey”, San Francisco, Intersection, 1975.
Other
edited by Di Prima. Various Fables from Various Places, New York: Putnam's, 1960.
translated by Di Prima. Seven Love Poems from the Middle Latin,, 1965.
edited by Arthur Edward Waite, introduction by Di Prima. The Hermetic and Alchemical Writings of... Paracelsus, New Hyde Park, N.Y.: University Books, 1967.
written in part by Sybah Darrich, Di Prima. Love on a Trampoline, New York: Olympia Press, 1968.
written in part by Robert M. Duffy, Di Prima. Of Sheep and Girls, New York: Traveller's Companion, 1968.
Audre Lord, Di Prima. The First Cities, New York: Poets Press, 1968.
edited by Di Prima. War Poems, New York: Poets Press, 1968.
edited by Di Prima, introduction by LeRoi Jones, Di Prima La Jolla. The Folating Bear: A Newsletter Cal.: McGilvery, 1974.
“Light / and Keats,” in edited by Anne Waldman, Marilyn Webb. Talking Poetics, Boulder & London: Shambala, 1978, I, pp. 13-37.
edited by Richard Grossinger. Alchemy: Pre-Egyptian Legacy, Millennial Promise, Richmond, CA: North Atlantic Books, 1979, pp. 26-33.
Periodical Publications
“Spring Thoughts for Freddie,”. Evergreen Review, 55 ( June 1968 ): 65-69, 82-83.
“Spring and Autumn Annals: A Celebration of the Seasons,”. Restau, ( 1970 ): 65-94.
“Street Like Stage,” UR, University Review, no. 33 ( December 1973 ): 19.
“Diane di Prima: An Interview,”. Intersection, 10 ( Spring 1980 ): 2-13.
Anne Waldman. “Interview with Diane Di Prima,” Rocky Ledge, no. 7 ( February-March 1981: 35-49.
Gene Detro. “Yin—,” Small Press Review, 8 ( June-July 1976 ): 70.
Polly Joan, Andrea Chesman. Guide to Women's Publishing, (Paradise, CA.: Dustbooks, 1978 ), pp. 134-136.
Susan Mernet. “Praying to the Loba,” New Women's Times, 15 ( April-May 1981 ): 1, 3.
Joel Oppenheimer. “Floating Bear,” Village Voice, 13 June 1974, p. 36.
David Rosenthal. “Art and Revolution,” Nation, 214 ( 3 January 1972 ): 24, 26.
Bill Zavatsky, review of Selected Poems, New York Times Book Review, 17 October 1976, pp. 32-36.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Persons:
Baraka, Imamu Amiri, 1934-
Subjects:
Naropa Institute.; New College of California—Faculty—Personal and professional papers.; Floating bear (New York, N.Y.: Periodical); Poetry—Editing.; American poetry—20th century.; American literatyre—20th century.; American poetry—periodicals.; Communal living—New York (State).; Beat generation.; Bohemianism—United States.; Universities and colleges—California.; New York (N.Y.)—Newspapers, periodicals, and journalism.; New York (N.Y.)—Cultural affairs—Literature.; California—Education—Universities and coleges.; California—Cultural affairs—Literature.; San Francisco (Calif.)—Cultural affairs—Literature.; Millbrook (N.Y.); New York (State)—Collective settlements.; San Francisco (Calif.)—Education—Universities and colleges.; Poems.; Diaries.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Books.; Personal Papers.; Manuscripts.; Publications.; Photographs.; Audiotapes.; Fliers (printed matter).
Occupations:
Poet.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
The materials were purchased in 1990.
Detailed Description
- Series I: Personal and Biographical Information, undated, 1934-1990
  - Address Book, ca. 1981 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - American Italian Heritage Association Conference, undated, 1988-1989 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - American Italian Heritage Association Conference, 1990 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - Bills and Receipts, undated, 1986-1989 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Biographical: CVs, undated (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - Buffalo Reading, 1983-1988 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - California Arts Council, 1988-1989 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
  - East Coast Tour, 1987-1988 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
  - Interview, 1980, 1985 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
  - Interview, 1985 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
  - Naropa Institute, 1988-1990 (Box 1:, Folder 11)
  - Naropa Institute, 1989 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
  - New College, 1985-1987 (Box 1:, Folder 13)
  - Notes, undated, 1990 (Box 1:, Folder 14)
  - Personal papers, 1934-1990 (Box 1:, Folder 15)
  - Poetry Project Symposium, 1990 (Box 1:, Folder 16)
  - Reviews and Interviews, undated, 1966 (Box 1:, Folder 17)
  - Reviews and Interviews, 1972-1979 (Box 1:, Folder 18)
  - Reviews and Interviews, 1980-1988 (Box 1:, Folder 19)
  - Ross Hospital Talk, 1990 (Box 1:, Folder 20)
  - Royalty Statements, undated (Box 1:, Folder 21)
  - San Francisco Institute of Magical and Healing Arts (SIMHA), undated (Box 1:, Folder 22)
  - SIMHA, 1982, 1986 (Box 1:, Folder 23)
  - SIMHA, undated, 1986 (Box 1:, Folder 24)
  - SIMHA, 1988-1989 (Box 1:, Folder 25)
  - SIMHA, 1990 (Box 1:, Folder 26)
- Series II: Writings, undated, 1966-1990
  - Subseries A: Diaries, 1966-1972
    - Millbrook Journal, 1966-1967 (Box 2:, Folder 27)
    - Millbrook Journal, 1967 (Box 2:, Folder 28)
    - Diary, 1972 (Box 2:, Folder 29)
  - Subseries B: Poetry, undated, 1982-1990
    - “Alchemical Fragments”, undated (Box 3:, Folder 30)
    - Buddhist Ruminations, undated (Box 3:, Folder 31)
    - Dream Poem, undated (Box 3:, Folder 32)
    - “Letter to Sheppard”, 1987 (Box 3:, Folder 33)
    - Loba Poems, 1990 (Box 3:, Folder 34)
    - The Mask is the Path of the Star, 1989 (Box 3:, Folder 35)
    - Miraj, 1988 (Box 3:, Folder 36)
    - New York poems, 1982 (Box 3:, Folder 37)
    - The Parallel becomes an Eagle, undated (Box 3:, Folder 38)
    - The Second Daughter: Li, undated (Box 3:, Folder 39)
    - Seminary Poems, 1988 (Box 3:, Folder 40)
    - Sonnets to Orpheus, undated (Box 3:, Folder 41)
    - Unidentified first drafts, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 3:, Folder 42)
    - Wyoming Series
    - Drafts and dummies, undated (Box 3:, Folder 43)
    - Paste ups, undated (Box 3:, Folder 44)
    - Galleys and Proofs, undated (Box 3:, Folder 45)
  - Subseries C: Prose, undated, 1969-1990
    - Memoirs of a Beatnik, 1969
      - Drafts (Box 3:, Folder 46)
      - Annotated manuscript (Box 3:, Folder 47)
      - Annotated manuscript (Box 3:, Folder 48)
      - Corrected page proofs (Box OS:, Folder 49)
      - Galleys for new edition, undated (Box 3:, Folder 50)
    - Robert Duncan's HD, 1989
      - Notes and drafts (Box 3:, Folder 51)
      - Talk to be published (Box 3:, Folder 52)
      - “Mysteries of Vision” (Box 4:, Folder 53)
    - Beneath a Single Moon
      - “Buddhist Anthology” (Folder 54)
    - Further Praises Anthology
      - Manuscripts, 1982, 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 55)
    - Recollections of My Life
      - Drafts, 1988, 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 56)
    - Material for David Metzler's Kabala (Box 4:, Folder 57)
      - (New College), undated
- Series III: Correspondence, undated, 1967-1990
  - Subseries A: Incoming, undated, 1967-1990
    - Aal, Katharyn Machan, 1987 (Box 4:, Folder 58)
    - Adams, Julie, 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 59)
    - Albert, Mimi, 1985, 1988 (Box 4:, Folder 60)
    - Alfonsi, Ferdinando, 1984, 1987 (Box 4:, Folder 61)
    - Alicia, Juana, 1983 (Box 4:, Folder 62)
    - Alonso, Barbara Moraff, 1976 (Box 4:, Folder 63)
    - American Voices Poetry Series/USF, 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 64)
    - Anderson, Jim, 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 65)
    - Andreae, Christine, 1985 (Box 4:, Folder 66)
    - Annis, Michael, undated, 1988-1990 (Box 4:, Folder 67)
    - Augustine, Jane, 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 68)
    - Aurell, Edie, 1987 (Box 4:, Folder 69)
    - Axelrod, Bruce, 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 70)
    - Barolini, Helen, 1985-1989 (Box 4:, Folder 71)
    - Basler, Sabra, 1987-1990 (Box 4:, Folder 72)
    - Beatty, Maria; Downtown Community Television Center, 1988 (Box 4:, Folder 73)
    - Belit, Liz, undated (Box 4:, Folder 74)
    - Beltrametti, Franco, 1976-1990 (Box 4:, Folder 75)
    - Bereson, Betty, 1987 (Box 4:, Folder 76)
    - Berkson, Bill, 1977 (Box 4:, Folder 77)
    - Berry, Kim, 1986 (Box 4:, Folder 78)
    - Bertholf, Robert, 1985-1986 (Box 4:, Folder 79)
    - Beyond Baroque Foundation, 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 80)
    - Birnbaum, Lucia Chiavola, 1987 (Box 4:, Folder 81)
    - Blackie and Son, Ltd., 1989 (Box 4:, Folder 82)
    - Blazek, Douglas, 1969 (Box 4:, Folder 83)
    - Boni, Giovanni, 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 84)
    - Boughn, Mike, undated, 1988 (Box 4:, Folder 85)
    - Boxer, Barbara, 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 86)
    - Brandstein, Eve, undated (Box 4:, Folder 87)
    - Branham Donner Ranch/Writing Workshops, 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 88)
    - Brillant, Alan; Unicorn Press, 1970, 1973 (Box 4:, Folder 89)
    - Brockman, John, 1982 (Box 4:, Folder 90)
    - Burk, Ronnie, 1985-1990 (Box 4:, Folder 91)
    - Butterick, George, 1986 (Box 4:, Folder 92)
    - Butula, Anna, 1988 (Box 4:, Folder 93)
    - California State University at Sacramento, 1987 (Box 4:, Folder 94)
    - Callahan, Eileen, 1990 (Box 4:, Folder 95)
    - Cameron, undated, 1976-1989 (Box 4:, Folder 96)
    - Canan, Janine, undated, 1987-1989 (Box 5:, Folder 97)
    - Capra Press, undated, 1973-1977 (Box 5:, Folder 98)
    - Carrillo, Lana, 1984 (Box 5:, Folder 99)
    - Carter, Janet, undated, 1988 (Box 5:, Folder 100)
    - Chandoha, Enrico, 1988 (Box 5:, Folder 101)
    - Charters, Ann, 1986 (Box 5:, Folder 102)
    - Charters, Sam, 1988 (Box 5:, Folder 103)
    - Chester, Laura, 1987-1988 (Box 5:, Folder 104)
    - Christy, Dave Alpha Beat Soup, 1988 (Box 5:, Folder 105)
    - City Lights Booksellers and Publishers, 1987-1990 (Box 5:, Folder 106)
    - Clarke, Cass, 1988 (Box 5:, Folder 107)
    - Clarke, Jack, undated, 1988-1989 (Box 5:, Folder 108)
    - Codrescu, Andrei, 1986 (Box 5:, Folder 109)
    - Cohen, Ira, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 5:, Folder 110)
    - Collier, Barbara, undated, 1988 (Box 5:, Folder 111)
    - Community Writers' Project, 1988-1989 (Box 5:, Folder 112)
    - Concordia, Lillian, undated (Box 5:, Folder 113)
    - Connor, Julia, 1977-1990 (Box 5:, Folder 114)
    - Consolo, Paula, 1983 (Box 5:, Folder 115)
    - Costello, Kitty, 1987 (Box 5:, Folder 116)
    - Cranston, Allan, 1990 (Box 5:, Folder 117)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1967-1968 (Box 5:, Folder 118)
    - Davis, Ron, undated (Box 5:, Folder 119)
    - Dawson, Fielding, 1979 (Box 5:, Folder 120)
    - Dee, Denise, 1986 (Box 5:, Folder 121)
    - deVries, Rachel Guido, 1986-1990 (Box 5:, Folder 122)
    - DeWitt, Bob, undated, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 123)
    - Dharmadhatu, Sangha, 1988-1989 (Box 5:, Folder 124)
    - Dietz, Elizabeth; Coffee House Press, 1990 (Box 5:, Folder 125)
    - Diggs, Lucy, 1987 (Box 5:, Folder 126)
    - Diluvian Bookshop, 1990 (Box 5:, Folder 127)
    - Dimen, Muriel, 1983 (Box 5:, Folder 128)
    - Di Prima Family, undated, 1985-1988 (Box 5:, Folder 129)
    - Distasi, Lawrence, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 130)
    - Doria, Charles, 1983 (Box 5:, Folder 131)
    - Doyle, Kirby, undated (Box 5:, Folder 132)
    - Dragos, William, 1982 (Box 5:, Folder 133)
    - Drew, Pippa, undated (Box 5:, Folder 134)
    - Drizhal, Peter (Urbanus), 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 135)
    - Dufresne, Isabelle (“Ultraviolet”), 1987 (Box 5:, Folder 136)
    - Dunbar, Jennifer, 1976 (Box 5:, Folder 137)
    - Duranon, Hilda, 1988 (Box 5:, Folder 138)
    - Eddington, Patrick, 1979 (Box 5:, Folder 139)
    - Evans, Virginia, undated, 1988-1990 (Box 5:, Folder 140)
    - Falchowski, Zelda, undated (Box 5:, Folder 141)
    - Feins, John, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 142)
    - Feller, Barbara, 1987 (Box 5:, Folder 143)
    - Fideler, David; Phanes Press, 1988-1989 (Box 5:, Folder 144)
    - Finstein, Max, 1963 (Box 5:, Folder 145)
    - Firebrand Books, 1987 (Box 5:, Folder 146)
    - Fishburn, Ellen, undated, 1987-1989 (Box 5:, Folder 147)
    - Fischer, Norman, 1987 (Box 5:, Folder 148)
    - Fitzgerald, “f-stop”, 1985 (Box 5:, Folder 149)
    - Fitzpatrick, Annie, 1986 (Box 5:, Folder 150)
    - Fleig, Cynthia, 1988 (Box 6:, Folder 151)
    - Fletcher, John, 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 152)
    - Foley, Jack, 1990 (Box 6:, Folder 153)
    - Forman, Janet, undated, 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 154)
    - Foster, Ed, 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 155)
    - Fouda, Alain Marlon, 1987 (Box 6:, Folder 156)
    - Fox, John, 1987 (Box 6:, Folder 157)
    - Franco, Michael, 1988 (Box 6:, Folder 158)
    - Freer, Stephen, 1987 (Box 6:, Folder 159)
    - Gardner, Joy, undated (Box 6:, Folder 160)
    - General, undated, 1979-1990 (Box 11:, Folder 402)
    - Gibson, Sharon, 1982 (Box 6:, Folder 161)
    - Gillan, Maria Mazzarotti, 1988 (Box 6:, Folder 162)
    - Gilliland, Mary, 1988-1989 (Box 6:, Folder 163)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, 1987-1990 (Box 6:, Folder 164)
    - Gooch, Brad, 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 165)
    - Gold, Joseph, 1974 (Box 6:, Folder 166)
    - Goldberg, Natalie, undated (Box 6:, Folder 167)
    - Grady-O'Connor, Panna, 1970 (Box 6:, Folder 168)
    - Grapes, Jack, undated, 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 169)
    - Grove Press/Fred Jordan, 1984 (Box 6:, Folder 170)
    - Guerriero, E.J., 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 171)
    - Gusanti, Joanne, 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 172)
    - Halifax, Joan, undated (Box 6:, Folder 173)
    - Harris, Zoe, 1990 (Box 6:, Folder 174)
    - Haug, Matt, 1986 (Box 6:, Folder 175)
    - Hawley, Robert (Oyez Press), 1970 (Box 6:, Folder 176)
    - Hayes, Kevin and Maria, 1989-1990 (Box 6:, Folder 177)
    - Hejinian, Lyn, 1987 (Box 6:, Folder 178)
    - Hekking, Angelina, undated, 1986, 1990 (Box 6:, Folder 179)
    - Hirschman, Jack, 1969 (Box OS:, Folder 180)
    - Hogan, Paul, 1985, 1988 (Box 6:, Folder 181)
    - Hoostraten, Harry, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 182)
    - Horowitz, Michael, 1985-1986 (Box 6:, Folder 183)
    - Hunter, Robert, 1980 (Box 6:, Folder 184)
    - Hutbunk, Anne, 1990 (Box 6:, Folder 185)
    - Intersection, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 186)
    - Irby, Kenneth, undated, 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 187)
    - Janssen, Susan, undated, 1985-1988 (Box 6:, Folder 188)
    - Jarnot, Lisa, 1988-1989 (Box 6:, Folder 189)
    - Jayyusi, Salma, 1988 (Box 6:, Folder 190)
    - Jones, Harriet, 1988-1990 (Box 6:, Folder 191)
    - Jordan, Betsy, 1982 (Box 6:, Folder 192)
    - Joris, Pierre, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 193)
    - Kanai, Debra, 1986 (Box 6:, Folder 194)
    - Karr, John, 1988 (Box 6:, Folder 195)